{
  "apikey": "%PUT-YOUR-API-KEY-HERE%",
  "description": "This is simple calibration data used for testing purposes. Do not use it in production environment!",
  "copyright": "Copyright (C) 2238 by BanAN Technologies Inc.",
  "test-data": [
    {
      "question": "32 + 39",
      "answer": 71
    },
    {
      "question": "69 + 78",
      "answer": 147
    },
    {
      "question": "74 + 51",
      "answer": 125
    },
    {
      "question": "11 + 9",
      "answer": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "99 + 9",
      "answer": 108
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 100",
      "answer": 157
    },
    {
      "question": "20 + 44",
      "answer": 64
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 43",
      "answer": 49
    },
    {
      "question": "32 + 84",
      "answer": 116
    },
    {
      "question": "32 + 5",
      "answer": 37
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 6",
      "answer": 16
    },
    {
      "question": "37 + 38",
      "answer": 75
    },
    {
      "question": "46 + 7",
      "answer": 53
    },
    {
      "question": "42 + 37",
      "answer": 79
    },
    {
      "question": "71 + 19",
      "answer": 90
    },
    {
      "question": "44 + 27",
      "answer": 71
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 63",
      "answer": 69
    },
    {
      "question": "58 + 27",
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "35 + 25",
      "answer": 60
    },
    {
      "question": "69 + 62",
      "answer": 131
    },
    {
      "question": "64 + 57",
      "answer": 121
    },
    {
      "question": "70 + 89",
      "answer": 159
    },
    {
      "question": "96 + 96",
      "answer": 192
    },
    {
      "question": "47 + 69",
      "answer": 116
    },
    {
      "question": "29 + 92",
      "answer": 121
    },
    {
      "question": "40 + 10",
      "answer": 50
    },
    {
      "question": "37 + 99",
      "answer": 136
    },
    {
      "question": "14 + 79",
      "answer": 93
    },
    {
      "question": "40 + 2",
      "answer": 42
    },
    {
      "question": "13 + 16",
      "answer": 29
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 24",
      "answer": 34
    },
    {
      "question": "58 + 35",
      "answer": 93
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 22",
      "answer": 26
    },
    {
      "question": "48 + 85",
      "answer": 133
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 21",
      "answer": 78
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 99",
      "answer": 102
    },
    {
      "question": "62 + 30",
      "answer": 92
    },
    {
      "question": "55 + 73",
      "answer": 128
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 52",
      "answer": 53
    },
    {
      "question": "38 + 29",
      "answer": 67
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 80",
      "answer": 87
    },
    {
      "question": "51 + 77",
      "answer": 128
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 44",
      "answer": 45
    },
    {
      "question": "96 + 44",
      "answer": 140
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 29",
      "answer": 86
    },
    {
      "question": "23 + 75",
      "answer": 98
    },
    {
      "question": "93 + 9",
      "answer": 102
    },
    {
      "question": "47 + 20",
      "answer": 67
    },
    {
      "question": "17 + 52",
      "answer": 69
    },
    {
      "question": "32 + 56",
      "answer": 88
    },
    {
      "question": "29 + 28",
      "answer": 57
    },
    {
      "question": "99 + 18",
      "answer": 117
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 28",
      "answer": 32
    },
    {
      "question": "81 + 74",
      "answer": 155
    },
    {
      "question": "77 + 64",
      "answer": 141
    },
    {
      "question": "87 + 56",
      "answer": 143
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 29",
      "answer": 101
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 94",
      "answer": 174
    },
    {
      "question": "97 + 51",
      "answer": 148
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 83",
      "answer": 89
    },
    {
      "question": "11 + 56",
      "answer": 67
    },
    {
      "question": "86 + 100",
      "answer": 186
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 40",
      "answer": 45
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 99",
      "answer": 155
    },
    {
      "question": "74 + 100",
      "answer": 174
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 35",
      "answer": 39
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 65",
      "answer": 145
    },
    {
      "question": "81 + 84",
      "answer": 165
    },
    {
      "question": "27 + 15",
      "answer": 42
    },
    {
      "question": "95 + 44",
      "answer": 139
    },
    {
      "question": "90 + 99",
      "answer": 189
    },
    {
      "question": "93 + 46",
      "answer": 139
    },
    {
      "question": "43 + 100",
      "answer": 143
    },
    {
      "question": "94 + 94",
      "answer": 188
    },
    {
      "question": "17 + 22",
      "answer": 39
    },
    {
      "question": "28 + 19",
      "answer": 47
    },
    {
      "question": "23 + 70",
      "answer": 93
    },
    {
      "question": "27 + 4",
      "answer": 31
    },
    {
      "question": "44 + 7",
      "answer": 51
    },
    {
      "question": "100 + 50",
      "answer": 150
    },
    {
      "question": "59 + 38",
      "answer": 97
    },
    {
      "question": "93 + 55",
      "answer": 148
    },
    {
      "question": "47 + 38",
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "55 + 73",
      "answer": 128
    },
    {
      "question": "37 + 24",
      "answer": 61
    },
    {
      "question": "64 + 43",
      "answer": 107
    },
    {
      "question": "48 + 37",
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 95",
      "answer": 128
    },
    {
      "question": "88 + 75",
      "answer": 163
    },
    {
      "question": "30 + 5",
      "answer": 35
    },
    {
      "question": "21 + 55",
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 61",
      "answer": 64
    },
    {
      "question": "63 + 25",
      "answer": 88
    },
    {
      "question": "64 + 11",
      "answer": 75
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 9",
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "71 + 8",
      "answer": 79
    },
    {
      "question": "35 + 79",
      "answer": 114
    },
    {
      "question": "11 + 10",
      "answer": 21
    },
    {
      "question": "3 + 17",
      "answer": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 17",
      "answer": 23
    }
  ],
  "chunk": {
    "number": 12,
    "total": 22,
    "size": 100,
    "range": {
      "from": 1100,
      "to": 1200
    }
  }
}